Hello friends, the chart of f4 India started from here
but its pimples
pattern started from here and its pimples
pattern was from here till here,
okay and this is the entire correction of this thing,
subscribe to the channel for all weeks
and press this bell icon,
so now I will show you its labeling, so
this will be its zero, this first web
and here it created its second and third
floors, then I did it later, so
you remove that also from the chart and friends, this is
our super cycle degree, okay, so this is the first
web of our super cycle degree
and this is the second web of our super cycle degree
and from here the third web of its super cycle
degree has come out, friends, this correction that you are
seeing, the second web of its super cycle degree,
this correction type is
called irregular affair, it is
a type of flat collection, this BA and
BSC, so this is a protection of irregular periods, so
from this place the
third web of its super cycle degree has come out and
friends, we will not talk about its target here,
breed it
with trailing stoploss, okay, broadly
you will see one in it  I am showing you the traveller intro,
friends, you should make a trend by combining this
point and this point on your chart,
that train will
come for you, this is a trail, friends, you should
keep it well because according to the rules of the new web, the
third day
cannot break 02111, so it means that in the coming time,
this trailer should not break until its third web is completed,
okay, so you should keep it on your chart
and in the coming time, you will
see that its trend will not break before the end of the third day, so
this was the
entire 9940 of Apple India, let's finish it in today's video
and if you definitely
want to comment, you can do it in the comment box below, see you
in the next video, till then
Jai Hind friends